Dusty Best

Web and Mobile Developer

San Diego, CA 92110 (619) 244-3491 dustybest@gmail.com

Fullstack developer currently enrolled at UCSD Extension pursuing a database management certificate. Experience with front and back end projects. Code school graduate and past volunteer at Open San Diego.

SKILLS

 Git / Node / Javascript / Wordpress / AWS / Azure / Angular / Photoshop / MySQL Server / CSS / HTML / Microsoft Office / Google / G Suite

EXPERIENCE

RadLocals, San Diego - Application Development Intern

JULY 2020 - PRESENT

- Mobile application development using Angular
- Translating Adobe XD mockups to functioning code
- Develop strategy for initial platform rollout

Softstack Factory, San Diego - Intern

JUNE 2019 - MARCH 2020

- Quality assurance and testing of learning modules
- Provide feedback regarding curriculum

Stone Brewing, San Diego - Server

MAY 2016 - PRESENT

High volume food and beer service

EDUCATION

Softstack Factory, San Diego - Certificate of Completion in Full Stack Web Development

NOV 2018 - MAY 2019

Softstack Factory is a full stack and data science bootcamp in down San Diego

San Diego State University, San Diego - Bachelor's of Fine Arts Multimedia

SEP 2007 - DEC 2011